Evil never gets old.
The Home is a mystery, horror, thriller film directed by James DeMonaco.
A troubled man starts working at a retirement home and realizes its
residents and caretakers harbor sinister secrets.
As he investigates the building and its forbidden fourth floor, he starts to
uncover connections to his own past and upbringing as a foster child.
Max, played by Pete Davidson.
Lou, played by John Glover.
Juno, played by Mugga.
Les, played by Adam Cantor.
Doc Sabian, played by Bruce Altman.
Sadie, played by Denise Burse.
The Home is a 2025 American psychological horror film directed by James DeMonaco, written by
DeMonaco and Adam Cantor, and starring Pete Davidson, John Glover, and Bruce Altman.
The film follows graffiti artist Max (Davidson), who works at a retirement home as part of his court-ordered
community service and begins noticing strange occurrences relating to the home's elderly residents.
The Home was theatrically released by Lionsgate and Roadside Attractions on July
25, 2025, and received generally negative reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of suicide, murder,
caretaker, foster child, retirement home.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.